Hello friends, I am Yogendra Verma, a health
insurance expert, I have been in this industry for the last 28 years
and I help people get the
best of the best products which are
coming out these days and all the workings. I
genuinely share new videos with you every day,
so please
subscribe to my channel, share and comment
because today I have brought one of the best plans of the industry for you, till
date
you would have never heard of such a big plan, nor would you have
ever seen it, nor would you have ever felt
that such a huge sum insured would be required in health insurance. I
also
guarantee this, friends, today I will
talk about ICICI Lombard's Max product plan,
whose four sum sums are available here -
1 crore, 2 crore, 3 crore, 5 crore, 10
crore and after that unlimited. Friends,
you might not have heard such a word before today that
it is written on the policy that
unlimited, no matter how big your claim comes, the
company will pay it completely. This is a big thing, that is,
how big a claim can come in health insurance,
1 crore, 5 crore, 10 crore or
even more.  So no one can even imagine how much it is,
that
unimaginable insurance
is also available at ICICI Lombard, which no
company in the industry has before today, if you
want, you can check it, it will not even be 10 crores,
I am talking about unlimited here, I will
tell you the reason why this is needed, I will tell you all the features of this policy, the
premium is very cheap,
very good and
global cover up to 3 crores is available in this plan for HNI segments, let's
quickly see
what you are going to get in this Max Product Plan,
number one, unlimited
sum insured product will be available
within affordable pricing, there will be a simple product
construct,
we will talk about the option premium plan
because there are two options here,
classic and premium, the company is selling only premium plan, so
we will talk about premium, there will be
unlimited coverage, the premium will be
affordable, all these working things are going to be available
here, you will get six such unique
features here which you will
not get in any company in the industry, number one, it will
beat medical inflation, number two  No
coverage limit, you won't have to worry about anything.
Number three: Access
to top health care. You can get
blind treatment done in any of the best, biggest and most expensive hospitals.
Number four: Coverage for various
medical expenses. You won't have to worry about any kind of medical
expenses.
Number five: World wide coverage up to Rs.
3 crore and 100% cashless. No co-op. This will be a
big thing in itself. Number six:
Reset benefit, that too in unlimited working
and guaranteed community bonus, which is
not available anywhere in the industry before today.
Every year, by default, whether the claim
comes or not, your sum assured will increase by Rs. 20 and
after increasing it will not be reversed. That is guaranteed.
Guaranteed in the policy. If I
talk more after these six features, then here you will get some such
compact features, unique features
which will be the best in the entire industry.
And what is inpatient 100% cover, day
care pre and post hospital for 60 days, 180
days, unlimited sum assured will be available. Rs. 1
crore, 2 crore, 3 crore  5 crore 10 crore
and after that the last sum shot will be
given in the name of unlimited. Guaranteed
cumulative bonus of Rs. 20 will be given up to a maximum of 100%.
Age treatment will be covered 100%, donor
domicile up to some shot will be covered, bariatric
surgery up to some shot will be covered, modern
treatment up to some shot will be covered up to a maximum of Rs.
1 crore and domestic road
ambulance will be covered up to Rs. 000 and tele-
consulting will be unlimited, unlimited
reset will be available, unlimited of any illness means
any illness and value added services will be
available in which there will be health assistant, there will be your
ambulance, there will be air ambulance, there will be deals
and discounts, all of that will be available in your value
added services and what are the other
features in it, world wide cover will be available up to Rs. 1 crore,
home care treatment will be available up to Rs. 1 lakh in air ambulance,
claim protector will be available, that is,
even if a claim comes, all your
expenses on consumables etc. will be covered 100%
here.  There will be preventive health checkup
up to ₹1000000 and the second option
for medical critical illness will be available
once for the same illness, you will be able to use it once in a year
for the same illness,
these are such big unique amazing features
which will not be available in any other company in the market, there will be
zone wise pricing here
Zone A Zone B Zone C Zone D If you have
taken premium of Zone A which is
in metro cities etc. on all over
India basis, then you will get treatment done in any zone,
you will not have to pay any copayment
but you
can go from upward to downward, if you go from downward to upward
then co-payment will be applicable, keep in
mind if you have taken C category
and you go to B then it will be charged at 16
and if you have taken B category and go to A then it will be charged
at 8 and if
someone has taken D category and goes to C for treatment then co-
payment will be charged at 16, so if
he does not get into the hassle of payment  If you want to study,
take the premium of Zone A. Get
treatment done anywhere without any co-payment.
I have already told you about the sum shot of
1 crore, 2 crore, 3 crore, 5 crore, 10
crore and unlimited option will be available.
Eligibility: People from 6 years to 65 years can
take it. Individual can also take it,
family floater can also be taken and here
anyone
can be added in the policy like grandfather, mother, grandmother, father in law, mother in law, mother father, brother sister, spouse, son daughter. Talking about child,
child cover will be available in the policy from 91 days to 25 years.
Talking about the waiting period, chronic disease will be
covered after 4 years. Specific disease will be
covered after 2 years. Ritual surgery will be
covered after 3 years and world wide cover, like if
you want to be covered outside India as well, then
you will be covered after 2 years. Not only this, if
you want your chronic disease to be
covered in less than 2 years instead of 4 years, then there is an option for this.  You
can choose the option of Reduce Pre-Existing Diseases, due to which your 4 year PD will be
covered in 2 years. If we talk about the room brand, then
you can take any room
except Accept Suite Room, you can
choose any room and if you want to go to a downgrade room, then
you can do it. We are
not talking about downgrade, we are talking about upgraded
room, so here upgraded is available, let's
talk about it. The policy can be easily taken for 1 year, 2 years, 3 years. You will
get a long term discount and if you take it for 3 years, then you will
get a discount of 10% for 2 years and 15% for 3 years respectively. And I have told you about the zones, A
B C D, zone wise pricing will be available here.
Medical test will be age wise and short wise will be
applicable before 55. If there is
one PD for up to 1 crore, then medical will be done on the
basis of tele screening and
if someone has more than one PD, then for the
age up to 55 years, we will take a fresh policy.
People are talking, so here below 60
medical test is mandatory, below 65 medical
test is mandatory and if there is no disease then
policy is available till 55 years without medical test, at the age of 1 crore or
more the underwriter will decide in which
case medical test will be triggered and in which case it will
not be, the company will decide and the
cost of medical test is borne by the company,
you do not have to bear it, if you
refuse after the policy is accepted
then you will have to bear the cost of medical test, whether you
get the policy or not,
in both the cases the company bears it, friends let's talk about the
premium because many people
complain that they
tell everything about the plan but do
not tell the premium, so I will give you an idea of ​​the premium also,
if someone is 30 years old today
and
takes an individual policy then the premium of a policy of 1 crore will be Rs
9277, if you take it for 2 crore
then it will be Rs 2146, if you take it for 3 crore
2 will come to 3658 and if you take it for 5 crores
then it will come to 24908, if you take it for 10 crores then it will
come to 2604 and if you take the unlimited option
then it will
come to 27708. Friends, there are age brackets here, there is
a bracket from 0 to
25, there is another bracket from 26 to 35, there is a
bracket from 36 to 45, there is a bracket from 46 to 50, from 51 to 55, from 56 to 60, from
61 to 65, from 66 to 70, brackets of every 5
years start after 45 years, so
in whichever bracket your age
increases, the premium will also
increase, so friends, you will get unlimited
sum assured for ₹ 708 as written in your policy,
which can be a big thing for an individual person, there is
not much difference in premium from 1 crore to 10 crores
and if I talk about 27000 from 1 crore  Even if I
talk about unlimited, the difference is only ₹ 8000.
Now let me talk about two
adults, so that you must have understood, if you
see the option of two adults, how much will be the
premium, if we take the age of 30 years
and if we talk about two adults, then the
premium for 1 crore will be
2886,
8186 if we see for 2 crores, then it will be 31531, if we
see for 3 crores, then it will be 34877, if we
see for 5 crores, then it will be 3618, if we
see for 10 crores, then it will be 3898 and if we
see the unlimited option,
for two adults at the age of 30 years, then the premium will be
40517,
4517 will be the final premium, I am telling you,
if we see for two adults to two children, then
how much premium will be, if we talk about the same age of 30 years,
if we talk about two adult to child at the age of 30 years, then the
premium  4378 will come 4380 will
talk for 2 crores 8978 will come 5 will
talk for 3 crores 4364 will come
5756 will come for 5 crores and if we talk about 10 crores then
6709 will come, if we talk about unlimited options then it will be
6386 this complete rate chart I will share with you
whatsapp2 plan so I will share all the details of the complete
plan with you and will guide you
friends this is the industry's best plan and the
expenses in health insurance in the
coming time people will have to increase their policy
in the coming time it will be very
small so if you do not want to face any kind of
problem or tension
want to beat inflation and
want to take such a tension free health policy
whose sum sum will never need to be increased then you can
take a sum shot of 1 crore to 10 crores or by default you can
choose the unlimited option from day one
because there will be so much power and working for you
that you will remain relaxed
in your mind that you have  Unlimited health
insurance is available which no
other company in the industry has. Again I am
talking to you with guarantee, so please
those who are serious about their health, are
serious about their family and want that if
my family gets any kind of
critical or normal disease, then I should
not have any tension or trouble, I should not have to think from
which best of the best
hospital I should get the treatment done, you
can get the treatment done from here without any hesitation,
for such tremendous power you will get
whatsapp2 plan and I will provide it to you genuinely,
we provide plan on all over India
basis,
this plan is genuinely available for the family members of customers outside India, NRIs,
Hello, your friend Yogendra
Verma